<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Addiction on Uma Ayer</title>
    <link>http://usayer.github.io/tags/addiction/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Addiction on Uma Ayer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://usayer.github.io/tags/addiction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How Remote Alcohol Monitoring Can Bolster Your Recovery</title>
      <link>http://usayer.github.io/publications/remotealcohol/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://usayer.github.io/publications/remotealcohol/</guid>
      <description>Remote monitoring allows for various members of the healthcare team to monitor test results; in fact, research has shown that sharing both positive and negative test results can help clients in reinforcing their abstinence to alcohol use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Effects of Spice Use</title>
      <link>http://usayer.github.io/publications/spiceuse/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://usayer.github.io/publications/spiceuse/</guid>
      <description>A Spice/K2 user is much more likely to experience serious adverse effects than a person smoking natural cannabis. These adverse effects may include psychotic symptoms such as paranoia and hallucinations. Furthermore, Spice use has been implicated in cases of kidney failure and heart attacks. With reported effects including reduced blood flow to the heart (myocardial ischemia), abuse of these substances can lead to severe and lasting heart conditions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Effects of Flakka Use</title>
      <link>http://usayer.github.io/publications/flakkause/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://usayer.github.io/publications/flakkause/</guid>
      <description>One of the newer chemicals in the booming category of synthetic or designer drugs, Flakka is typically made from a synthetic version of an amphetamine-like stimulant in the cathinone class called alpha-PVP. People who use Flakka can display cases of bizarre and uncontrollable behavior.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ativan Rehab Centers And Addiction Treatment Help</title>
      <link>http://usayer.github.io/publications/ativan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://usayer.github.io/publications/ativan/</guid>
      <description>Ativan (generic name: lorazepam) is a benzodiazepine drug often used for the short-term treatment of anxiety, insomnia, and sedation of hospitalized patients. When misused, Ativan can lead to addiction and can have hazardous long-term consequences on a person&amp;rsquo;s life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vicodin Rehab Centers And Addiction Treatment Help</title>
      <link>http://usayer.github.io/publications/vicodin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://usayer.github.io/publications/vicodin/</guid>
      <description>Vicodin is a combination medication containing hydrocodone and acetaminophen. Similar trade name formulations include Norco and Lortab. Hydrocodone is an opioid agonist, a type of drug that relieves pain by attaching itself to receptors in the brain and interfering with pain signals. It’s also a Schedule II controlled substance, meaning it has a high potential for abuse and dependence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vyvanse Rehab Centers And Addiction Treatment Help</title>
      <link>http://usayer.github.io/publications/vyvanse/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://usayer.github.io/publications/vyvanse/</guid>
      <description>Vyvanse works by increasing norepinephrine and dopamine activity in the brain, which affects attention and behavior. Though it was created as a less addictive and longer lasting alternative to first generation ADHD treatments such as Ritalin and Adderall, Vyvanse can be abused.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;K2 Domain of the Lysine Gingipain (Kgp)&#39; in ActiveModels Library to accompany Garrett &amp; Grisham: Biochemistry, fifth edition.</title>
      <link>http://usayer.github.io/publications/k2domain/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://usayer.github.io/publications/k2domain/</guid>
      <description>Porphyromonas gingivalis is an obligately anaerobic bacterium recognized as an agent of adult periodontitis. P. gingivalis produces cysteine proteinases called gingipains, proteases that break down both proteins and cytokines. The Lysine gingipain, or Kgp, is the most potent fibrinogen/fibrin degrading enzyme of the 3 gingipains in human plasma and is involved in the bleeding tendency at the diseased gingiva.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>